{
    "subject": "resource/Pierre-Gilles_de_Gennes",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Paris",
    "human_readable": "Pierre-Gilles de Gennes was born in Paris.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9549048542976379,
            "question": "Name the city where Pierre-Gilles de Gennes was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9223359823226929,
            "question": "Where was Pierre-Gilles de Gennes born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6115598082542419,
            "question": "What is Pierre-Gilles de Gennes known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38862287998199463,
            "question": "What are some of Pierre-Gilles de Gennes's notable contributions to science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3873231112957001,
            "question": "Which field of study did Pierre-Gilles de Gennes specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3204011023044586,
            "question": "What is the name of Pierre-Gilles de Gennes's most famous theory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3164966404438019,
            "question": "Did Pierre-Gilles de Gennes work at any universities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3000674545764923,
            "question": "In what year did Pierre-Gilles de Gennes receive the Nobel Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25500577688217163,
            "question": "What was the subject of Pierre-Gilles de Gennes's Nobel Prize lecture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24686451256275177,
            "question": "What prestigious award did Pierre-Gilles de Gennes win?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pierre-Gilles de Gennes was born in Paris.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7169_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the subject of Pierre-Gilles de Gennes's Nobel Prize lecture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7169_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Pierre-Gilles de Gennes receive the Nobel Prize?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7169_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Pierre-Gilles de Gennes work at any universities?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7169_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7169_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7169_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7169_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7169_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7169_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7169_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7169_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7169_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7169_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7169_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that \"Pierre-Gilles de Gennes was born in Paris in 1932.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}